RESUME

Shashi Kumar V.P.O.Rajot, Teh.Baijnath,

Distt.Kangra State.Himachal Pradesh.India-176063.

E-mail: maniram1970@yahoo.com

Mobile:-+91-9779675271

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To acquire professional edge through hard work and continuous learing. Seeking an interactive and challenging environment for creativity and introduction of revolutionary ideas, where I can apply my strengths, interpersonal skills and an opportunity for personal growth and professional advancement in the field of accounts.

CAREER HIGHLIGHTS

Extremely well-organized and efficient. Quickly learn procedures and methods. Able to develop and implement new systems when necessary. Strong bookkeeping and managerial experience. Capable of handling projects concurrently. Excellent public relations and customer contact ability.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

From October, 2011 to December, 2012

Harinder Investments Ltd. Jalandhar. Its deals in Finance, Loan, Deposits & etc.

Position: Accounts Executive Reporting: Accounts Officer

Job Profile:

- Billing of Loan & Deposit in Solution Accounting Software
- Preparing Service tax and Tds Related work.
- Routine Accounts Related work in Tally & Excel
- Preparing MIS Report
- Store Management
- All Official Documentation & Administrative Work

From April, 2013 to May, 2018

Akal Academy Makhangarh (100% Institutions work)

Position: Accountant Reporting: Head Office

Job Profile:

- Routine Accounts Related work in Tally & Excel.
- Preparing Tds Related work.
- Preparing MIS Report.
- Preparing The Cash Book, Bank Book Manually & Computerized (in Tally)
- Preparing All Voucher of Employee's
- Preparing Salary sheet with the deduction of epf, security.
- Preparing Bank Reconciliation
- Routine Bank Related Work
- All Official Documentation & Administrative Work.

From June, 2018 to till date

Takshila School (100% Institutions work)

Position: Accountant Reporting: Head Office

Job Profile:

- Routine Accounts Related work in Tally & Excel.
- Preparing Tds Related work.
- Preparing MIS Report.
- Preparing The Cash Book, Bank Book Manually & Computerized (in ERP)
- Preparing All Voucher of Employee's
- Preparing Salary sheet with the deduction of epf, security.
- Preparing Bank Reconciliation
- Routine Bank Related Work
- All Official Documentation & Administrative Work.

From June, 2018 to till date (Part time work)

Gagandeep Singh CA

Job Profile:

- Income Tax Return
- TDS deposited and Return file
- Routine Accounts Related work in Tally & Excel.
- Preparing Good & Service Tax and Tds Related work.
- Preparing The Cash Book, Bank Book Computerized (in Tally)
- Routine Bank Related Work

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

- Passed Bachelor of Arts in June, 2011.
- Pursuing Bachelor of Commerce.

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATION

- Passed Diploma of Accounts & Finance in July, 2008.
- Passed Spoken English Course.

KEY SKILLS

- Computer Software Know
 - 1. Strong in Ms-Office (Word, Excel & etc.)
 - 2. Strong in Tally as well as ERP Accounting Software
 - 3. Strong in Solution Accounting Software
 - 4. Strong in Busy Accounting Software
 - 5. Average in Marge Accounting Software
 - 6. Average in FMCG Logic Accounting Software

Father's Name Late Sh.Mani Ram Date of Birth 9th December, 1986

Marital Status Married Nationality Indian

Interest and Activities Reading, Computer and Music

Language Known English, Hindi and Punjabi

Strength Smart Worker in Our Work and Confident

DECLARATION:

I declare that all the above details are true to the best of my knowledge and belief. If given chance to serve in your esteemed organization, I will keep no stone unturned with sincerity, honesty and smart work.

(Shashi Kumar)